I theorize that we are watching the fall of the United States be exacerbated by the world banking system with the goal of being able to put in place a central banking system, i.e. a currency that is shared by the entire world.
Like the petrodollar was a version of that, and now they want to like up the stakes.
It's like they have to make the petrodollar fail in order to introduce something else that's even more controlling.
But in order to do this, like there has to be global compliance.
That's why Iran is such a big deal.
When you look at the countries that don't have a central bank, they're all countries that the U.S. has either currently invaded or previously invaded to take control of and completely destabilize.
With the help of Israel and other European nations.
And I believe that the reason why we're seeing countries like Switzerland all of a sudden be like, oh my God, the U.S. is so whack.
And like taking an actual stance, mind you, Switzerland is where the world banking system is home base.
So the Masons, the International Monetary Fund and the World Central Bank all share the same building in Switzerland.
So it's literally neutral because it's base.
Okay, now we see that.
Then we also see like all these cardinals who are the U.S. cardinals for the Pope, who is the first American Pope.
We see them like saying like, oh my God, like the U.S. is so whack, is so whack, is so whack.
And we know that the Vatican and these families are also connected to the hand that Black Rocks, the cradle, that is controlling the entire world and its resources.
Okay, so this has always been part of the plan and it was in our history books.
And so I know that this is a conspiracy theory and that's fine because we should be theorizing the conspiracies that are happening that are putting us in dire straits so that we can consider where our actions can be put.
I really feel like what we're watching is an effort to make the United States an agent of chaos so that it brings about a need for someone to save the world from the United States or something or somewhere or some way.
And the hands that are running shit, they run the United States.
The oligarchs who run the United States, like it's not Zuckerberg, it's not Bezos, it's not these people that are visibly out here.
Those are faces to distract you.
The people who run the United States and make the decisions to sanction countries to death, who make the decision to have Congress put all this money into death,
they are the ones who are the grounding the foundation of the stock markets and who control the federal reserves.
And they run the Vatican and they run the International Energy Agency.
So they run all the things that are saying that the United States is wilding.
Well, if you run both of them hoes, then there's a conspiracy happening.
So that's my theory. I'm big on the zoom out of things.
And when I see deviations from trends and patterns, it pricks my awareness, as it should always prick yours.
And so that's where I'm at.
By the way, they did the same thing with England.
They paid for the Revolutionary War.
And then they funded World War II, which completely destabilized Europe and allowed for the United States to come in and be like a world savior.
And next thing you know, there's the birth of the United Nations, which has literally just been a ruse to make folks think they're a part of some democratic process of the world that they're not actually a part of and that they're shown on a regular basis that they're not a part of by nature of the Security Council being able to veto by literally just one vote.
I think I'm right.
Support a real one.